Beach, Kenneth, Papers /3055
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kenneth Beach Papers
1929-1953
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Beach, Kenneth
/3055
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Course materials, correspondence, tests and results of the Bigelow-Sanford Institute of Industrial Relations conducted by the school at the request of Bigelow-Sanford Company. 1952-1953. And a scrapbook of the Hotel Statler training course.
3078931
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 21, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4297: ILR School Biography Files
Beach, Kenneth M.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations -- Faculty
3078931
- Correspondence Bigelow Institute of Md. Management, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Conference June 3-4-5, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Organized Charts, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Function Delineation, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Peterson's Speech, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Photographs of the BIIM Group (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Scope and Contents
  Photograph
- Management and the Community Progress Report Accomplishments of Bddm, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Papers, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Publicity, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- MacTavish's paper on Executive Develop. Programs, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bigelow-Sanford Citizen of Amsterdam, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Bigelow-Sanford Carpet Company Inc., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Bound
- Meet Your Company, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bigelow-Sanford Carpet Company (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Amsterdam Evening Recorder, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Bigelow-Sanford Carpet Company, Inc., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Bigelow-Sanford Carpet Company, Inc., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Bigelow-Sanford Carpet Company, Inc., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Bigelow-Sanford Carpet Company, Inc., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Open House at Bigelow, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Historical Background of Floorcovering (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Bigelow Today, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Interviews: First Series, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Allen, Harvey (Harr), 1952 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Barkley, Don (Don), 1951 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Curran, Thomas (Tommy), 1953 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Donnelly, Eliot (Eliot), 1953 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Fallar. Edward (Ed) (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Gagne, Edward (Ed), 1953 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Grunewald, Richard (Dick), 1951 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Harris, Kenneth (Ken) (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Henry, C. Kenneth (Ken), 1951 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Huff, Thomas (Tom) (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Jones, Robert (Bob) (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Lembo, Michael (Mike) (Box 1, Folder 35)
- McQuigan, Edward (Ed), 1953 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Robert Levitch (Bob), 1953 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Mumma, James (Jim) (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Packard, David (Dave) (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Plumley, Frank (Frank) (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Russo, Carl (Carl) (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Schneider, Raymond (Ray) (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Sertl, Francis (Frank) (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Smith, Felix (Smitty) (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Ward, William (Bill) (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Wurz, Harold (Harold), 1953 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Interview with Associates (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Interview Records (Box 1, Folder 48)
- BIIM Cost Control Questionnaires Progress Review Human Relations Progress Review, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Students' Evaluation of the Courses (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Workload Questionnaires Supervisory Situation Survey, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Evaluation of the Reading Program Completed Questionnaires, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Test Results (Box 1, Folder 53)
- "Management Qualifications" Questionnaire (19), 1951 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- "Management-Community Relations" Questionnaire (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Elements of Supervision, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Business Economics, 1929-1950 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Community Relations, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Mimeographed Instructional Materials, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Hotel Statler (Articles), 1950 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Hotel Statler (Articles), 1950 (Box 2, Folder 1)